Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No animals were harmed during
the filming of this series.
85th episode
In the name of Mighty Allah...
...who makes anything happen as he says...
...and fills our hearts with faith.
In the name of Allah.
Ordeal and difficulty.
These are like valiant men.
They never get close to those less
strong than them.
They saw as equals...
...so they never leave us alone.
We survived many troubles, hardships.
But it is time...
...to tell this tyrant to stop.
Vizier Alemşah...
...and Geyhatu.
They are so cruel that...
...they don't stop when you tell them.
Now the way to stop them is...
...the sword of justice.
Their sentence is death.
My Osman Bey...
...the Vizier settled in Söğüt
as if it is his.
Soldiers are everywhere.
How can we take it back?
Vizier can be managed.
Söğüt is the property of Kayı.
But how we will take Geyhatu...
...from twenty thousand nökers...
...my Bey?
Only Söğüt?
Who holds the far lands?
You see...
...they ride their horses on our property
without our permission!
Before...
...those nökers come...
...we will hit them at their safest time.
Master Davut...
...how many swords have you
crafted so far?
I crafted five for each valiant of
the tribe.
Praise be!
Akça Shepherd...
...tell me...
...how many jugs do we have to hit
the oppressor?
Fifteen of them are ready, my Bey.
I can make forty more if I will have time.
Thank you.
This is war.
People will die and get injured.
Kumral Abdal...
...do we have enough medicine, ointment
and bed?
All of them are ready as you ordered,
my Bey.
May Allah protect our alps!
Amen!
Measures and preparations are done.
But troubles will follow us.
This won't end with Alemşah and
Geyhatu.
I thought Alemşah did all these for his
own benefit.
But he had another ally to his cruelty.
Who is it, my Bey?
Tell us, my Bey.
Do you think of anyone, my Bey?
Tell us, my Bey!
Söğüt
Rebellious Beys are with Osman Bey,
Vizier Alemşah.
Uğur Bey and his brother İvaz are also
on their way to the tribe.
İvaz's daughter is on her way too.
In that case, we will be quick, Güngör.
We'll take the shepherd out and shoot
him before his flock grows.
Loyalty is a rare quality.
But the hardest thing is choosing to whom
you are loyal.
Since they chose Osman, they all will end
up the same.
What are you planning, Vizier Alemşah.
There is someone loyal to Osman
among us.
But if the traitor doesn't know
his betrayal is revealed...
...he also won't know to whom he serves.
Erbey, call Konur!
Osman will be dead before İvaz arrives.
Now go. Traitor shouldn't see you.
Go and handle İvaz.
All right, Vizier Alemşah.
There will be no one left unhandled.
You first handle your brother!
You are no different from a dog!
Who can it be?
Is there anyone more degenerate
than Vizier?
Who is it, my Bey?
What does he get by working against us?
We don't know who it is for now.
Sultan Mesud...
... thinks that I tried to kill him.
Before he believes this lie and
comes after me...
...I will find whoever did it and...
...take care of it.
My Bey...
...what should Kayı's beys do until then?
Order us, my Bey.
Start the war preparations.
Get armed.
Alps must start the drills.
And train their children to become
a man.
As you order, my Bey!
We will get strong as a wolf, my Bey!
No one can go against us now!
Thank you.
Only Kayı's beys, Osman Bey?
Me, my alps and my tribe is always ready
to fight by your side.
I know, Turgut Bey, I know.
You have fought by my side
for a long time.
But Beys...
...must listen to me before starting
the preparations.
Alps' responsibility and order...
...no longer belongs to Gündüz Bey.
Turgut Bey...
...proved himself...
...many times...
...in the plain of Konya and
at the Lord's Castle.
Thus, he is now the head of the Alps
in Söğüt and in Kayı Tribe.
As Osman Bey sees fit.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
May my Rabb grant me the honor of
fulfilling this duty.
-Amen! Amen!
I hope.
Geyhatu lost breath while running from me.
Now...
...it is time for his last breath.
Beys, you can start the preparations.
You stay, brother.
Come in, Konur.
Yes, my Vizier?
Osman is at his tribe.
Did your spies lose their eyes, Konur?
Reduce the number of soldiers.
We won't be alone while raiding the tribe.
We will go over the Wolf hill and...
...secretly meet Geyhatu.
As you order, my Vizier.
Erbey...
...go after this dog.
Make sure he tells Osman about the plan.
See it with your eyes.
As you order, my Vizier.
Fulfill your last duty to me, Konur.
Lure Osman to my trap.
I promise you that...
...I will hang you with Osman, to whom
you are loyal!
Brother...
...do you resent me...
...for taking your duty away?
No way, Osman Bey.
I have no right to resent.
I have no goal other than helping you and
making up for my mistakes.
Thank you, brother.
Thank you.
People make mistakes.
You are entrusted to me by my father
Ertuğrul Gazi.
I entrusted you the tribe.
But you made a mistake, brother.
I know that...
...your intention...
...was to keep the tribe safe and
get the least harm you can get.
Your intention was good.
But your move was wrong.
You always want what's best for the tribe.
But the best happens...
...when you choose the right way, brother.
Therefore...
...I make you Kayı's Bookkeeper.
Brother, Allah knows...
...I would accept if you made me a
guardian at the door after what I've done.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Stay by my side...
...support me...
...open your eyes wide...
...and we will fight together, brother.
Your cause and way are of Allah.
I am by your side, brother.
You will glorify the tribe.
You will make new trade roads...
...new agreements.
But you will do these without bowing...
...without turning your back
on the people...
...and without being deceived, brother.
I have full faith in you.
I will do whatever it takes to glorify our
tribe, brother.
Believe me.
Thank you.
Hello, Akça Dervish.
Hello, Konuralp. Welcome.
Inform Osman Bey at once.
Don't worry, Konuralp.
Be quick, Akça Dervish.
He needs to receive it immediately.
Akça Dervish...
...be careful.
Vizier's soldiers may watch you.
May Allah help you, Osman Bey.
Konya Palace
Vizier Alemşah told me to convey this
to you, my Sultan.
As if it wasn't enough you tried to kill
Geyhatu and...
...inflicted Argun's wrath on you,
you also work with the Emperor, huh?
You told me there were traitors.
I almost believed you and forgot you tried
to kill me!
There is no greater traitor than you,
Osman!
We are going to the Kayı Tribe!
As you order, my Sultan!
Osman!
Welcome, Konur.
You should've sent our greetings
to Osman Bey.
Konur!
Now the truth is revealed!
Vizier Alemşah!
What does this mean?
You know what it means better.
You've disappointed me greatly, Konur.
You traitor!
You went behind me looking into my eyes!
You are the traitor!
You work for yourself,
not for the State of Seljuk!
Thankfully I could see your true face!
You, Vizer Alemşah...
...are a hypocrite devil!
Loyalty is not easy.
But the hardest thing is choosing to whom
you are loyal.
You are a traitor Konur!
You worked with Osman and assassinated
the Sultan!
When I get Osman...
...I will cut his head and send it
to Sultan with yours!
Your treachery worked, Konur!
Now I am luring Osman to a trap
thanks to you!
Speak, Alemşah, speak.
You are the most despicable
of degenerates!
You will pay for all you have done!
Allah is the best of those who set a trap.
Throw this dog into the dungeon!
He won't get a piece of bread,
a drop of water.
He should learn the price
for betraying the state!
I didn't betray my state,
I served my state!
That state is the state Osman Bey will
establish!
O Allah...
...make my Aladdin Ali grow...
...like a sapling in the garden of Islam.
May he be a valiant walking on the Islam's
road.
My Rabb...
...may you grant my Allaaddin Ali
a healthy and right life.
Amen, my Osman.
Son! Son!
I wrote this when I found out
I was pregnant.
Ayatul Kursi.
My Alaaddin Ali!
What a beautiful name for my son.
My wish is that...
...you follow the right path like
Hazrat Ali.
May you be a companion to your brother
Orhan.
Don't ever hurt each other.
Be a son worthy of your father Osman
Bey...
...and always be by your brother's side.
What a great prayer, Bala.
You have the heart of gold.
I already can see how a great son
you will raise.
I wish that...
...even if they are apart, their hearts
are still one.
Alaaddin Ali, you have such a beautiful,
such a brave mother that...
...you are so lucky.
I hope...
...you follow your grandfather
Sheik Edebalı's road.
You will be the other light of our tribe,
son.
Amen, my Osman.
I hope so.
Can I come in, my Bey?
It is important, my Bey.
Come in!
My Bey...
...Akça Dervish brought this.
It is from Konur.
Vizier!
So you go to Geyhatu, huh?
I will get you!
It is time.
We will hit the road.
We will finish that Vizier.
As you order, my Bey.
Inegöl Castle
Doesn't this ''Don't kill the messenger.''
phrase belong to the Turks?
Then, what is this?
What is this?
That Vizier!
He became such a barbarian after Geyhatu
but...
...everything in this life has a price!
If he didn't accept me...
...if he is this brave...
...all right.
Then, I will set a new plan and...
...deceive Osman.
Karakus, prepare my horse.
I am going to Kosses.
To traitor Kosses!
As you order, Sir.
Stop!
-Where are these good going?
-To the bazaar, my Bey.
We are at war. You don't sell this much
goods when at war.
What will people eat if the tribe
gets sieged?
It is your order, my Bey.
You told us to sell the goods before
waiting.
That time is over. Now, it is not about
money.
It is about preparations, alps.
Erdoğdu...
...from now on, you will check every good
going to the bazaar.
Nothing will be on Kayı's stand before I
check it.
As you order, my Bey.
Come on. Return.
-Check who it is.
-Yes, my Bey.
Stop!
Who are you?
Selvi Hatun, İvaz Bey's daughter.
Welcome, but we need to search
the carriage.
For precaution.
Alps!
Selvi Hatun is Malhun Hatun's cousin.
And our guest.
-Don't keep her waiting.
-As you order, Gündüz Bey.
-Welcome, Selvi Hatun.
-Thank you, Gündüz Bey.
Hatuns will accompany you to the tent.
Thank you.
Come in.
Gee up! Gee up!
Gee up!
Vizier Alemşah!
The tyrant's time has run out!
How do you know, Osman?
Does time belong to you?
You are the one who lived longer
than he should.
I will die for my dream, Alemşah!
It will always stay as a dream, Osman.
Because we are after the same goal.
Two swords cannot fit in one scabbard.
Erbey!
Alps!
Vizier!
Osman Bey, this way!
Come on!
Alps! Come on!
Go after them! Kill them all!
Come on! Come on!
Osman will not leave here alive!
Come on!
Osman!
Osman Bey!
Valiants, follow me!
Of course, our friends helped too.
So you set a trap, Osman!
What turns the dream into reality is
the idea that comes to mind...
...to reach the heart.
You set traps for us and we took measures.
Thank you, Turgut Bey.
Thank you.
Attack!
Vizier!
The punishment of the traitor is clear,
Konur. You did this to yourself.
What kind of a man are you?
Let's talk when my hands are untied.
You betrayed the state!
You worked with the rebel Osman.
You deserve worse!
Do you do this because I deserve it
or because you are afraid?
No one could save you from me if my
hands weren't tied.
Do you think I am dumb, you traitor?
Are you trying to deceive me?
I know what to do with you!
You are dumb! So dumb that you believe
The Vizier's lies...
...and turn your back on the truth!
You have done so much.
Not only to me.
He intended to kill the hatuns of my tent.
You spilled the blood of...
...you spilled the blood of my mother.
Vizier.
Come here!
Come!
You separated my son, my
Orhan from his mother.
I haven't forgotten the
things you've done.
You made Maria run away.
Did you think you weren't
going to pay for all of this?
I did all of that.
But did I do it all alone?
Your brother was in on all of it.
I know how you tricked my brother.
I know his intentions.
But,...
...I will kill you with your own poison.
If you don't kill me here...
...I'll do worse, Osman.
This time I won't separate
your child from his mother...
...but I'll bury him in the ground.
I'll kill you for that sentence alone.
But you got things to say.
You'll breathe until you say those things.
Geyhatu will kill you
for doing these things.
When he hears about it.
Don't you worry at all.
I'll get him too, thanks to you.
Konur.
You wait Selvi Hatun...
...I'll inform Malhun Hatun.
So this is where you live, Malhun.
It's not enough being a mother, you also
want to be a khan for the government.
You always set your sights high anyway,
the best tents of the tribe were always...
...set up for you.
The fastest horses were given to you.
But all of that will change.
I've had enough staying in
your shadow all this time.
You'll see who is the
daughter of a bey, Malhun.
Selvin, after the last moves Osman made,
these lands have gotten more dangerous.
Don't worry, I'll end those
who are in my way.
Watch Osman's tribe very carefully.
Who is close to who...
...or more importantly,
who is distant from who?
Learn that well.
We need to know where to break
those that are united like Kaya.
Malhun is such an arrogant hatun that she
doesn't even see my hatred towards her.
She doesn't even see
the rage I have against her.
That's why she won't
hide anything from me.
Selvi, don't let your rage
hinder your duty.
You should go before for our goals.
Watch the tribe and send me word.
Don't have any worry, my bey.
Malhun's life is always
at the edge of my dagger.
There is no death before making
her suffer more than I had suffered.
Don't worry about me,
come safely after me.
Selvi sister!
Malhun, sister!
Welcome!
Happy to be here sister!
They're not worthy of you, but...
...accept them.
You shouldn't have, sister.
Thank you!
Tell me, what brings you here?
I want the good news, sister.
My uncle Umur Bey is on the
way he'll be here by sunrise.
After that Ivaz Bey will be here
along with the entire tent.
We're together from now on, sister.
What are you saying Selvi?
Where is my father right now?
On his way, sister, do not worry.
Thank goodness!
Welcome back!
ON THE WAY TO KERVANSARAY
Umur Bey is like an uncle to me.
Greet him very well innkeeper. Make sure
the table is flowing with milk and honey.
The food and the drinks are ready.
Everything has been done the
way you ordered, Barkın Bey.
Good.
Let's make sure it's a great service.
He should have arrived by now, Hüsamettin.
I'm sure he'll be here soon, my bey.
My bey, Umur Bey is here.
Umur Bey is a blessed man, Hüsamettin.
He came the moment we uttered his name.
He won't let us miss him any longer.
Umur Bey.
Thank goodness, Umur Bey!
We've been waiting for you.
- Welcome!
- Good to be here, Barkın!
You will pay for what you've done, Osman.
I got over my suffering, Vizier.
Now, you will pay for the things
you've done, one by one.
Now, wait here!
That rope will be wrapped around
your and Geyhatu's neck.
I'll take your reputation first...
...then, your life.
Konya will make you pay...
...for what you've done
to Konya's Vizier, Osman.
I welcome them, Vizier.
I welcome them.
Umur Bey, have you missed here?
I even missed the air here.
Even though I just came back...
...I missed these sacred lands.
The great Allah...
...may he grant me to
see those lands again.
If Allah permits, my bey.
If Allah permits, my bey...
...we'll pray at hajj together.
If Allah permits.
Nephew, where is Selvi?
He wanted to go before me, Umur Bey.
She missed Malhun Hatun so much.
Bless her.
Turk's heart always leads.
It doesn't suit them to stop, right?
What do you think?
What is it that brought us here?
Fifty times stronger than the
ones that get stuck on wood.
We'll tear Küffar limb from
limb if Allah permits.
If Allah permits.
Is this enough, Akça?
Put plenty of it.
Put plenty of iron so
that no tyrant is standing.
Exactly!
Put plenty of fire and iron.
They didn't hold back their cruelty,
why should we hold back our rage?
We'll do whatever our
conquest-loving heart wants.
We'll spill their blood on these lands!
These fires will burn our enemies good!
May Allah bless you Kumral!
All Muslims will unite!
All Turks will unite!
Dervishes from one side,
sister warriors from the other!
The alps from one side
soldiers from the other!
We'll be the end of our enemies and the
hope of the oppressed if Allah permits!
Allah Allah! Allah Allah!
It's important to be the
hope of the oppressed.
That comes with killing the tyrants.
We will if Allah permits.
Thank Allah who granted
with me comrades like you!
Thank you all!
The ones who have the same
goal become comrades, Raşid.
Now, we'll keep the
promise we gave to Allah.
The entire Muslim world will be one.
The worshippers will
stand up to the tyrants!
Our path, our cause is Islam!
It is to spread Islam to the whole world!
It is time to make the
tyrants get on their knees.
It's time to make the
tyrants bow their heads.
With the help of Allah,
we will defeat the tyrants!
The worshippers...
...you will achieve your
goals with Allah's help.
Have no doubt.
Allah is the greatest!
It's almost over.
Raşid, you get the horse carts ready.
We're going to see Osman Bey!
We're going to burn our enemies!
Allah Allah! Allah Allah!
May Allah bless you!
It's the inland that makes these
lands important, Umur Bey.
As horse trail gets mixed
up with dog trail...
...The Turk's hope is draining away.
- But...
- What but?
We are fed by dreams.
Loyalty cannot raise on this land.
The essence of loyalty is order.
Loyalty is nothing without order.
Becomes stronger with the conscience
of the bey who is the head of the people.
Umur Bey...
...it seems easy to set up an order
when you're looking from far away.
Even establishing a government seems easy.
But I'm not so sure.
So you say...
...that Osman Bey is drinking
water from a river of dreams.
Keeps drinking and not
getting fooled right?
- Osman Bey...
- Shush!
Tell me Ozan
What did Osman Bey do?
Osman Bey made the lands countries.
His cause is our cause.
The water he drinks is
from the rive of truth.
Thank you!
He is from Kayı Tribe.
He's been a friend to me for a long time.
If you could just see uncle Umur,
he keeps talking about the Holy Land.
He loved the Kaaba.
He'll go back to the Hajj as soon
as he handles his business here.
Who wouldn't want to see those holy lands.
May Allah grant us with
that too if Allah permits.
- Amen!
- Amen! If Allah permits, aunt.
Malhun Hatun, are you well?
You look faded.
I'm well Ayşe Hatun.
I felt strange when we
talked about my father.
It's from excitement, my sister.
Umur Bey kept talking about Osman
Bey's courage and about you.
He says he won't be content if
he doesn't see Orhan before he dies.
Allah forbid!
- But he will see him if Allah permits.
- If Allah permits.
If Allah permits.
May I come in?
Come in my girl.
Bala, what's going on my girl?
Why did you come back
this early from the tent?
I can't sit at the tent all day mother.
I'm well.
Welcome Selvi Hatun!
Happy to be here Bala Hatun!
Sit, Bala.
I've heard about your reputation
and about your beauty Bala Hatun.
Praise be! You're even more
beautiful than what I've heard.
I've heard from Malhun
that Orhan has a brother.
May he be healthy.
May he live long if Allah permits.
Amen!
- Amen!
- Thank you, Selvi Hatun!
Look at Allah's work...
...wait for all this time
and not have a child...
My Creator's actions
are not questionable, daughter.
So, tell us.
Who is your fiancee?
Your father Ivaz Bey wouldn't see
anyone suitable for you.
How did he permit?
Barkın Bey is from our tribe,
Selcan Hatun.
He is beloved in the tribe.
He is so warm and lovely.
When the tribe loved him,
my father's thoughts changed.
He was convinced.
Loyalty is appropriate when there are
Beys like Osman.
Then you can build the order
and the state.
Wrong!
Kill them all!
Order is corrupted!
Fear exhausts our souls.
- You will fear!
- Shut up!
Damn the day we accepted you
in our tribe!
Harmankaya Castle
You are one of the most royal Lords
this lands will witness.
Aya Nicola.
Are you that desperate?
Friend, huh.
Your only friend is your interests.
You don't need to play with me.
I read your mind word by word.
Now that you can read...
...you should see that I am happy to
be ally with you and even Osman Bey.
I see, Nikola.
Unfortunetaly, when I look at you, the only
thing I see is a devil in disguise.
Okay, Kosses, if it was not for
those devils, it would be boring...
War, war, war and more war!
Also, I don't think Osman Bey prejudges
as much as you do.
Although we have been enemies for years,
I think he is happy to ally with me.
Osman Bey trusts me.
Doesn't he?
Speaks Latin
Nikola.
Trust causes trust.
Osman trusts you as much as you
trust Osman.
No more, no less.
Not everyone is like Samuel.
He made sure of our trust
even when he was at the opponent's side.
Allow us, Lord Kosses.
News from Osman Bey!
Come in Kyros!
Osman Bey's alp arrived, sir.
Osman Bey invites you to his tent.
He wants Lord Nikola as well.
Me?
Of course, with pleasure.
Right, my dear friend?
Not without you.
Prepare the horses.
Let's not keep Osman Bey waiting.
I told you Mingeon.
Vizier Alamshah has the control of
Osman now.
Geyhatu has been waiting for this moment
for a long time.
He will not kill Osman easily.
Osman! Osman!
Osmannnnnn!
Come again!
Osmannnn!
Osman.
Ya Osman!!
Loyalty starts with fear...
...grows with order!
I'll make these lands fear me!
Only cowards fear!
I am an old man.
Don't you know that...
...you can't fear an old Alp
with sword!
Come at me, Barkin!
Come at me!
Fear lets one stay alive.
The one who is afraid can do
anything to live.
Look.
How fearful they are!
If they weren't afraid, they might have
escaped while I was busy with you.
Sister.
Is there something wrong in the tribe?
Alps are everywhere.
They searched the carriage too.
Our tribe is under threats, daughter.
A rose garden contains many thorns.
We have lots of trouble.
Sometiems Lords, sometimes Mongols.
And that Alemshah!
He nearly set us against each other!
Thank Allah you came just in time,
Selvi Hatun.
Osman Bey went to call them to account.
Tell us, how is it like
in your lands?
How many tents will you bring?
Our tribe has 500 tents, Selcan Hatun.
We have 1000 cavalries with old men
and young men.
Good, good.
Our lands are like as you know.
Troubled as always.
Our lands need valiants.
We need valiant hatuns like you.
Ivaz Bey's arrival will strengthen
the whole Turkmen tribes!
Inshallah. (If Allah permits)
Barkin Bey!
Every alp died from Kizilbeyogullari.
We killed our alps who disobeyed as well.
Whoever disobeys my commands
are not my alps anymore!
My valiants!
Why did you kill my alps!
Not your alps, think about yourself,
Umur Bey.
He is a valiant man.
You've seen it, didn't you?
How I slaughtered the Mongol dogs!
Traitor!
Why did you kill my
valiants?
Do you hear what he says?
He says "my daughter Malhun".
He salutes her.
Orhan?
That one you kept talking about even
though you've never seen?
He says hug my Orhan for me.
He says, "smell him".
Sure, Umur Bey.
I'll hug your...
grandson for you...
tightly...
Orhan!
My father-in-law...
will share the same fate.
Come on.
Umur!
Ihvaz!
Osman!
They are talking about order and unity!
But they don't know...
unity comes from chaos!
I'll burn the borders...
I'll break their walls...
they'll have no chance but
to join me.
We won't leave our future
to dreamers.
I'll rule with fear...
and might!
Brothers!
Ihvaz Bey will share the same
fate with Umur Bey.
And Osman.
Long live Barkın Bey!
Hüsamettin.
This is our quarters now.
Prepare it.
What are you doing here?
We'll blow it up.
Brought to you by historicalfuntv.com
Finally, I made you kneel.
You'll face the most painful death, Osman.
You'll face infinite suffering in hell.
I'll skin you alive...
I'll send your parts to rebellious beys.
I'll be an example.
But the Kayı; Gündüz's betrayal,
your insolence...
I'll destroy the Kayı.
I'll cause your extinction, Osman.
Gündüz Bey is detoxicated.
Don't hold back.
Even if we are no more, someone
will hold the flag of Islam.
But you won't die before the plots
you built with that vizier.
I will kill you with my own hands.
Stubborn Turk.
Speak like this when I skin you alive.
I'll kill your inheritor and you,
just like this.
I'll cut your face first.
Like Bilāl ibn Rabāḥ...
we only serve Allah.
Even if your tyranny rises to the sky...
it can never stop us.
Allah is good!
-Allah is righteous!
Geyhatu, I have you now.
I'll put you and Vizier Alemşah
in a cage.
If you kill me,
Argun will come.
Then, forget the Kayı, not a single
Turk or Muslim survives.
Forget Argun Khan, even if Kubilai Khan
comes from Hanbalık, he can't save you.
Alps!
Bury the dead.
Take the wounded as captives.
Share the horses and weapons.
Wait!
The best archer I have.
Before my enemy releases a single arrow,
you shoot three.
But...
is your tongue as tense as your bow?
You know my secrets.
Don't you?
Yes, my bey.
This is bad.
Bad.
My secrets are too heavy for
you to carry.
You shouldn't have learned them.
You shouldn't have.
Now, whatever you know...
it will go to the grave.
A wolf that can get into
a herd alone.
Tell me, what are my goals?
Breaking the order that is built, my bey.
One who knows my goal,
knows my secret.
I said it. My secrets are heavy.
My bey's tent is this way.
The tent of the brothers is
this way.
Then, the white tent will be far.
If I set it here...
it will be far from my bey's.
Allah Allah!
Cerkutay!
Cerkutay, why are you wandering
around like crazy?
You are wounded.
Have you forgotten about it?
I haven't, my wife.
I haven't.
I'm thinking where to set our
tent.
I was going to call you
when I see a place.
-Why are you thinking? Just do it.
-No. It's important.
It's very important.
Let me think a little longer.
Don't think, Cerkutay.
Close your eyes. Shoot it.
And let's be done with it.
I should?
Do it.
I should think.
Let me think.
I wanted you to shoot it.
Come on.
Go and set our home.
I'll accompany Malhun Hatun and
Özge Hatun.
I'll set it?
How can I set it like this, mad girl?
She is mad!
And the home...
Cerkutay will build it.
They had a use...
Hüsamettin.
What are you proud of?
Of my loyalty.
I'm proud of my loyalty, my bey.
Why did these men die?
You killed them for me to understand how
valuable I am as a loyal man.
These valiants who fought
alongside me for years...
maybe they would never
betray me.
But I killed them for you, Hüsamettin.
You can be loyal.
Don't forget what will happen to
you if you go astray.
Never forget this.
Osman Bey is coming!
Welcome, my bey!
Welcome, Osman Bey!
Osman Bey, we thank Allah for you!
His soldiers killed my husband.
May Allah bless you for bringing
him like this.
It's the responsibility of a man
who is after justice.
Thank you.
Long live Osman Bey!
Brought to you by historicalfuntv.com
What did Osman Bey do?
He equipped the sword of justice!
He protected the oppressed!
What did Osman Bey do?
He made the tyrants kneel!
Defeated the ones who fought
the Turks!
What did Osman Bey do?
He destroyed Geyhatu and Alemşah!
Mashallah!
O' people!
We fulfilled our promise.
Thank Allah.
These two haunted who were
trouble for the Turks...
are in front of you now.
One from outside...
the other...
the other is one of us.
But now, they are under my sword
of justice now.
Long live Osman Bey!
Now, take Geyhatu and Vizier Alemşah
to my tent.
Before they breathe for the last time...
I have things to say.
Don't worry!
They won't die so easily.
But...
but there are things we need
to find out.
Who is Vizier Alemşah working with?
We need to learn this.
After then...
I'll behead them both.
When Geyhatu dies...
there will be incomers from
Turkmen tribes.
Then...
this state that we'll foun for
the order of the world will born here.
Long live Osman Bey!
Mother Selcan!
Mother Selcan, help!
-What is it?
-Orhan has a fever.
What are you saying, my daughter?
Bala! Stay with Alahaddin.
Selvi, Bala is a new mother.
Don't leave her.
A border bey's mission is obvious.
It's becoming a wall and
protecting the lands.
When you find an opportunity,
it's raiding the enemy.
It's not stabbing your sultan
on the back!
You have done such a treachery,
Osman...
death is an escape for you.
Now, you have no place in Seljuk lands.
You will be dragged after horses but
won't die, Osman!
All the revolter tribes will take
example from you!
Will your emperor sit after
you rebel?
I'm coming, Osman.
I'm coming.
I'm coming to make you pay
for your treachery.
Orhan, what happened to you,
my child?
You are burning.
Alright.
You are burning, my child.
My Orhan.
Malhun?
Is Orhan alright?
Mother, my child is burning!
I can't lower his fewer.
Alright.
What will we do, mother?
He is burning!
Alaca, prepare water with vinegar.
Come on.
Alaca, hurry!
Alright, my child.
Alright.
May Allah protect you.
Mother, does his fewer go down?
He is a child, my daughter.
Of course, he'll have a fever.
My child.
Don't cry, my baby.
Allah is healing.
This won't do.
Ayşe, go and prepare
soft water...
for Orhan.
Alright.
Orhan, my child!
My child!
Malhun, strip him.
Kervansarai on the Road
You did well, Barkın.
The borders are saved from
another trouble.
Ihvaz is next.
Is it not enough, Barkın?
What are you doing, idiot?
Are you afraid of me?
Why should I?
You will be.
I'll make you pay for
this, Barkın!
I spare your life against your
insult.
Will you make me pay
for two alps?
What insult?
Did I kill Umur for gold?
You can't buy me!
You can't rule me!
Are you afraid?
Send my regards to Vizier Alemşah
and your brother.
I'll visit them both soon.
What happened will be
our secret.
You are so coward that...
you can't go around without
an armor.
You are afraid...
that your dark soul will
leave your weak body.
Geyhatu.
See how coward your
partner is.
Osman will die, Gündüz.
But you...
you will pay dearly
for your treason.
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah, we returned from our mistake.
But this won't be your option.
Do what you will, Osman.
Kill me if you want...
speak if you want.
Not me.
Nikola will do that.
He'll tell the dagger
you pulled against each other.
I'll be honored.
This Vizier Alemşah is a funny man!
Oh, Geyhatu...
Geyhatu the wise.
If you heard what Vizier Alemşah
said about you...
which you will hear soon.
This vizier...
came to my castle.
Nikola, he said...
I'll erase this barbarian Geyhatu
from these lands...
I'll gather all the lords...
and banish him from here,
forever!
Shut up, Nikola!
Stop poisoning Geyhatu with
your lies.
Vizier Alemşah!
Give the devil his due!
I'm a good liar but...
Vizier Alemşah, there is much that
I can learn from you.
I mean, building this alliance for
too long and not revealing this?
Right?
My only wish...
was a just order.
To bring stability to these lands.
You don't have what it
takes to do that.
With a good way or
an evil way...
that's all I wanted.
Vizier...
You are like a doctor who
kills.
You love power.
But I...
I took your power.
And now...
you are trying to survive...
but I'll take your soul out.
Alemşah!
You said that in your order...
only the ones who can kneel
will stand.
Is this what you mean?
You would profit the most, Gündüz.
But now, you won't even have
a tent to sleep in.
I'll raze your tribe.
My brother and Nikola would profit, huh?
What about the flying fire that you
brought to destroy the walls?
You were going to take what yo
want and destroy the lords and the beys.
Osman, will you kill me
by talking?
Pull your sword and end it.
No.
Geyhatu.
You won't die easily.
Firstly...
firstly, you'll see what this
vizier was up to.
Then, you'll hear his suffering.
You made people suffer.
You won't die before suffering.
Who poisoned your warriors?
Who attacked you apart from us?
Attack!
If not you? Who, Osman?
Who?
Thank Allah, he is better.
The milk did him good.
Thank Allah.
He got tired from crying.
He sleeps so well.
Mashallah.
Mashallah to my brave.
Ayşe.
In the name of Allah.
Come on, my girl.
Mother. Ayşe Hatun.
Thank you.
Sit with your child, my girl.
Mother's precious.
My baby.
Oh, my Orhan.
You made me scared.
May Allah bless you.
May Allah protect you.
My dear son.
Soon, my Orhan.
Your grandfather will come.
Are you being shy because
of your grandfather?
See, he'll love you so much!
Oh, oh!
Great Umur Bey!
Who is more of a wolf than a wolf,
brave Umur Bey!
Many weasels tried to bite
your grandfather but...
he broke their fangs with
his hands.
Even the ones who set traps to
sow discord among your father and I...
were destroyed by him.
Your grandfather is mighty like that!
The one who poisoned your warriors...
is someone who works with Alemşah.
You came there.
How did you know it?
How?
Get him up.
Take them away.
This vizier...
will await his death now.
I'll talk to Geyhatu personally.
Now...
I sowed discord among them.
To survive, they'll sell each other out.
Finally, victory is ours.
Your part in it is doubtful, Nikola.
If you mean the war...
I retreated to
gather strength.
For that, my part might be a little
bigger than yours.
And also...
I'm grateful that you didn't ashame
me against the emperor.
Those who stand with us
don't get ashamed, Nikola.
Let him know that...
the danger is over but you couldn't
get rid of a Turkish bey.
Vizier Alemşah, Geyhatu...
Osman's enemies are dissappearing
one by one, Kosses.
That's what we wanted, Nikola.
Was it really, Kosses?
Osman used us and captured
all his enemies.
Who's turn is it now, Kosses?
You know it too.
It's our turn.
He'll turn to our castles first.
Then...
he'll attack us.
If I go now...
and tell Osman...
and he cuts you...
I would feel so good.
And I would be protecting
my castle too.
One stone, two birds.
Tell me, Geyhatu.
How I will kill you?
I heard that a lot.
What I want to hear...
is Argun Khan.
Argun will kill you Osman.
You wanted to protect this
little land...
all the tribes will burn
because of you.
Argun Khan...
sent an envoy to the west,
to the Europeans.
What is his goal?
What is it?
Was it a secret?
You are so afraid of the
Turks and Muslims...
for that reason, you want to
ally with the Christians.
So, you aren't as strong as you say.
These lands are easy, Osman.
But world domination requires
alliances.
Why are you working with the Emperor,
the lords?
You are small. You are with the small.
We are big, Osman.
Your big ally is Vizier Alemşah?
You don't even know who to ally.
His life is precious.
Sooner or later...
he'll say everything.
Vizier is small.
And so is his mind.
He betrayed me.
If you don't kill him, I will.
I'm big, Osman.
If you kill me, you'll see
how big I am, Osman.
You are big.
Is it why you are my captive?
I'll teach this to
all my children.
They shouldn't be above themselves.
Allah is greater than everyone.
Do you know Allah, Geyhatu?
In a moment of carelessness...
those you call small will
take you down.
I will kill you, Osman!
A dog can't bite a wolf.
When Genghis' grandchildren
hear that Geyhatu is dead...
they'll charge here to destroy
you and your lineage.
Then...
you'll see the dogs and
the wolves, Osman!
We'll see.
When the last tribe burns...
you will regret all this, Osman!
Regret!
Brought to you by historicalfuntv.com
Come on.
Come, brothers.
Come.
Cerkutay, what are you doing here,
brother?
Eat, Cerkutay, eat.
Leave some for us, brother.
I'm hungry, brother.
I'm hungry.
What are saying, Cerkutay?
Isn't Aygül Hatun cooking for you?
Brothers.
Marriage...
is harder than the wedding.
Brothers.
Keep in mind...
listen to me now...
keep in mind...
Take care of yourselves!
Aygül Hatun is waiting
for food.
Aygül Hatun is waiting for food.
Cerkutay!
-Salam Alaikum, alps.
-Alaikum Salam.
Cerkutay. I yelled at him but
he didn't look.
I hope it's good.
His trouble is great, Akça Dervish.
What are those?
Gündüz Bey sent it. It's the spoils
left from Geyhatu.
You fought bravely. You earned
these.
Thank you.
Your mother loves you, Orhan.
Never forget that.
Welcome, Osman.
My lion!
Come here! Come, come, come!
I was so afraid, Osman.
I didn't know what to do.
It's good that Mother Selcan arrived.
It's over now, Malhun.
It's over.
My lion is healthy.
Kumral Abdal said it.
It's how he'll grow up.
Thank Allah.
And his fire isn't from his body...
but his heart.
He'll be a fierce warrior.
His grandfather is a warrior, his father
is a warrior. Of course he will!
He even held the sword!
Our prophet, when he smelled
his grandchildren...
he would get the
smell of heaven, Bala.
Now, I know what heaven smells like.
I also get the same smell, my sheik.
Gratitude! My Allah gave me this joy.
Thank Allah!
Thank Allah, my daughter!
Now...
my grandchild Alahaddin Ali is
like fertile soil.
The seeds you will seed on him...
will be the fruits you'll get one day.
His reach is truth.
Science and knowledge will
be his two wings.
-Inshallah.
-Inshallah, my sheik.
He won't be alone on this road.
His brother Orhan will always
be with him.
By the way...
-How is our Orhan?
-His fever is gone.
-He made us afraid but he is good now.
-Thank Allah.
-May I enter, Malhun Hatun?
-Come, Alaca.
Is Orhan alright?
He is, thank Allah.
His fever is gone.
Thank Allah.
-Any news from my father?
-No, Malhun Hatun.
But he must be close.
He'll be here soon.
Stay with my Orhan and inform
me if something happens.
Thank Allah, your grandfather
is here, my Orhan.
Thank Allah!
-Father!
-Umur Bey...
No...
Uncle!
Umur Bey!
We are in this world as subjects.
Surely, we'll return to him.
Father.
What happened to you, father?
What happened to you?
Seeing you like this...
Is this how you come to
see your grandchild?
Barkin! What happened to my uncle?
Who did this to my uncle, Barkin?
Speak, Barkin!
Who did this?
What's happening?
Tell me!
We were ambushed, my Bey.
Mongols attacked.
We tried to defeat them, but
they were crowded.
Kizil Bey's son Umur Bey.
You set your heart to die in battle field.
Your prayers came true, father.
Your prayers came true.
May your shahada be blessed.
I am not to cry!
Our condolences, Malhun Hatun.
May his shahada be blessed.
May Hadrat Hamza accompany him
in the afterlife.
Amin.
Our condolences, Malhun Hatun.
May his shahada be blessed.
Amen.
Don't talk!
Don't cry!
Never cry after a martyr!
My father has met shahada.
His prayers he prayed all his life
came true.
No one is to cry!
Bring me those two dogs!
Yes my Bey.
Baysungur, come on.
Take his body inside.
Malhun.
Traitors!
You had the power.
But you didn't use it in the right way.
You paved the way for...
...cruelty all around the world!
You have taken many innocents'
and my alps' lives!
Now it is time.
Osman.
Argun will erase you from history
if you kill us.
If you kill me...
...you are not going
to be acquitted, Osman.
Do not be a fool because of your pain.
Sultan is coming!
Sultan Mesut is coming!
What are you going to do now, Osman?
You can't dare to kill us
in front of Sultan.
You are not that brave.
Mesut will not permit.
You should have killed us when you
had the chance, Osman.
My Sultan.
What is happening, Osman Bey?
Are you going to kill Commander Geyhatu...
...after intending to kill me?
Are you going to kill Alemshah,
Vizier of the state?
Does your rebellion have a limit at all?
Hadrat Sultan Mesut.
I told you about everything...
...before the spy of those two dogs
hit you.
They were standing with you
in order just to continue their betrayal.
However, it is apparent that...
...my words have not influenced you.
Do you want me to believe your lies...
...or believe what I see with my own eyes?
Explain it all now!
You sided with Lords...
...and had an agreement with the Emperor.
- My Sultan...
- Enough!
Release Geyhatu and Vizier!
You are going to be judged in Konya!
My Sultan.
Many innocent died while waiting
for you to...
...open your blinded eyes!
Your shall unblind your eyes!
The blood of cruels shall shed!
Mercy on the cruel...
...means betrayal to the innocent!
Osman!
When the lies end...
...truth rises.
It is not the time to be deceived.
Everybody will...
...see the truth.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com